{
    "subject": "resource/Glionitrin_A",
    "predicate": "http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#label",
    "object": "Glionitrin A",
    "human_readable": "The label of Glionitrin A is Glionitrin A.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9787205457687378,
            "question": "What is the label of Glionitrin A?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8270419836044312,
            "question": "Is there more information available about Glionitrin A?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8236466646194458,
            "question": "Are there any known uses for Glionitrin A?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7457275986671448,
            "question": "Is Glionitrin A a chemical compound?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7398244738578796,
            "question": "What research has been conducted on Glionitrin A?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.732098400592804,
            "question": "What are the potential applications of Glionitrin A?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6946776509284973,
            "question": "How is Glionitrin A categorized scientifically?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6331696510314941,
            "question": "What properties might Glionitrin A possess?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5478651523590088,
            "question": "Could Glionitrin A have biological significance?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5210902094841003,
            "question": "Are there any known risks or side effects associated with Glionitrin A?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The label of Glionitrin A is Glionitrin A.",
            "html": "dbpedia_357_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Could Glionitrin A have biological significance?",
            "html": "dbpedia_357_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What properties might Glionitrin A possess?",
            "html": "dbpedia_357_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How is Glionitrin A categorized scientifically?",
            "html": "dbpedia_357_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_357_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_357_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_357_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_357_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_357_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_357_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_357_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_357_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_357_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_357_76.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Given the context information, I'll evaluate whether the information supports the triple \"The label of Glionitrin A is Glionitrin A\".\n\nThe documents mention \"Glionitrin A\" repeatedly, but they do not discuss its label. The label refers to a specific name or identifier given to a compound.\n\nBased on this understanding:\n\n* The document mentions that \"Glionitrin A and B are two molecules with properties that make them useful tools in drug development.\" (This suggests the names of the compounds are Glionitrin A and B, but it does not imply what their labels are.)\n* There is no mention of a label for Glionitrin A.\n\nTherefore:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple stating that the label of Glionitrin A is Glionitrin A."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The claim is wrong because the label of Glionitrin A was confirmed as Glionitrin A by comparing its 1H- and 13C-NMR, optical rotation and electrospray ionization mass spectrometry (ESI-MS) data with previously published values for Glionitrin A.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}